<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Wired Blog</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Wired Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Again 001</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/again-001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/again-001/</guid><description>So I&amp;rsquo;m here again, rebuilding in a massive backlog of failures, one again and again there is still people cheering up on me I was thinking could be a normalized depression field or this is normal in me I feel like I made so much progress only to see nothing out nothing new same view and now I must go out because my time here is up? is been always up, no more of me here I guess.</description></item><item><title>Tradeoff</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/tradeoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:45:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/tradeoff/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to make tradeoff At least for me, and i have to the choice of having someone to have fun or someone that really understands me, so i keep myself the same way but . . .
I still looking for memories to fill the endless void of my curiosity.
&amp;quot;I feel alive not gonna lie&amp;quot;So no hard feelings and let it go, huh? Is that so?</description></item><item><title>Tryhard-Reborn Protocool</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/tryhard-reborn-protocol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/tryhard-reborn-protocol/</guid><description>I hear Jerusalem bells A-ringin' Roman cavaldry choris are singing!The first thing I did this morning was sing, lungs out, I feel so much discomfort I must die, this must end, no more.
Les's see if the Grit has and end.I must face my fears and burn my dread in order to ascend
I must burn the stigma no and for all - It&amp;rsquo;s unfair It&amp;rsquo;s weird but if that so.</description></item><item><title>Test 002 Ja Vi</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/test-002-ja-vi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/test-002-ja-vi/</guid><description>test
Connection established. Transmission complete.
Present day, present time. Another entry logged into the wired&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Krill Eater</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/krill-eater/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/krill-eater/</guid><description>Many species of ==whales, seals, penguins, fish, and squid== rely on krill for their survival.
But i think the image is a shrimp, anyway I love Crustaceans, hard shells, lots of arms, everywhere.
So this small fella is so useful in quantities and we don&amp;rsquo;t even understand how they even effect the whole global ecosystem, there is a pasive or a talent for a character I like in Dota 2, it&amp;rsquo;s called Tidehunter, is a sea monster humanoid form but huge, well when you pick this pasive you start like a small fry and start gaining more size and strength.</description></item><item><title>Subito - Capito</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/subito---capito/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/subito---capito/</guid><description>El tiempo pasa, muy Rapido y muchas veces no nos damos cuenta no solo de él si no del impacto de otras vidas en la nuestra.
Estoy agradecido, de retribuir la confianza que pusieron en mi.
Gracias totales que el mar de Ether no diluya tu impresionante presencia.
Connection established. Transmission complete.
Present day, present time. Another entry logged into the wired&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Good morning Vietnam</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/good-morning-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/good-morning-vietnam/</guid><description>I wake up early this morning, is cold, I&amp;rsquo;m barefoot- underwear, and my long coat, I hate eating in the morning makes me feel all bloated , also drugs hit better with a empty stomach I hear my many alarms sound over and over, but I&amp;rsquo;m awake - I&amp;rsquo;m here, i can turn the off one by one but after hearing them , I must know the time I&amp;rsquo;m wasting or spending.</description></item><item><title>Computers and more machines</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/computers-and-more-machines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0400</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/computers-and-more-machines/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re part of the moon of the light of every atom I interact with and I&amp;rsquo;m so i&amp;rsquo;m love I can&amp;rsquo;t scream I can&amp;rsquo;t speak I never been so tight of hands of mind of love . . . Oh dear I wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready for any of this but I&amp;rsquo;m still here
HEre
I&amp;rsquo;m like a ship that never left that nobody wants
so in the air
left to rot</description></item><item><title>Corrupt Data 062</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/corrupt-data-062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/corrupt-data-062/</guid><description>I got so used to run that I&amp;rsquo;m still on it #I&amp;rsquo;m soo fill with pain, with hate, with love, they don&amp;rsquo;t stop so getting more intense.
shorty shorty shorty shorty, get the fuck out of my mind is not a place for you. I mean why lit me up? why burn the pyre why the rot expands ticking seconds, less telomers for me and you, tell me inmortal machine, how it feels a empty eternity with not promised afterlife?</description></item><item><title>Danna's Mission</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/dannas-mission/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/dannas-mission/</guid><description>KAli install for defensive Lesson 1) head to https://www.kali.org2) click on download a get the ISO3) Use [RUFUS](https://rufus.ie/en/) to burn the iso into a usb4) plug it into the desired device // kali can run a live version limited but with some cool tools5) install it and start trying pen testing and more! 💯🛰️🐦‍⬛🧱💀🐀🐭🐁🍷⚡🦈https://github.com/vinta/awesome-python A lot of python stuff and functuinalitiesside quests:
Open a github account Create first repository Create first integration (bot?</description></item><item><title>Corrupt Data 001</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/corrupt-data-001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/corrupt-data-001/</guid><description>Se supone que me deberia sentir mejor no asi. no asi. ¿porque? ¿es culpa mia?
So i can say she want solo, you can say, cuz she can get way
I wanna get rid of all, all these feelings, all these memories I wanna be painless, soulless as you say you are. Do you feel, pain do you?
I feel every tissue screaming for something real and this is not this is just a DEAD END FABRICATED DEAD END NO WHERE TO RUN IMPROVE</description></item><item><title>Rosemary</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/rosemary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/rosemary/</guid><description>Hard to say last time i feel like this . . . So alive, so in pain, so regretful and hateful at the same time, hand filled with love, heart pouring all of this and the funny part is that my mind doesn&amp;rsquo;t even think is real.
What you did to me?
This chain of events that you trigger is making me so primordial, so basic, naive, simple. tasteless even though is just in a deeper level .</description></item><item><title>La Dama de Hierro no Puede dormir!</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/la-dama-de-hierro-no-puede-dormir/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/la-dama-de-hierro-no-puede-dormir/</guid><description>Siempre atenta siempre vigilante, La dama de hierro no puede dormir, ella mira siempre al horizonte, buscando, 1000 batallas fueron ya, ¿900? no se puede saber, su cuerpo cubierto de hierro esta.
El hechizo que la hizo tan fuerte, no la deja descansar, el oxido, mella, corroe, duele.
Aquí estoy, cierra los ojos un segundo yo miro por ti, deja la lanza descansar, Dama de hierro en batalla ya no estas, flores en ti crecen, Dama de hierro siempre fuerte, descansa, Dama de hierro en batalla ya no estas, mira la hoguera no forja espadas, el rey no comanda, las flechas no se venden y tu debes descansar.</description></item><item><title>finally!</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/finally/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/finally/</guid><description>1 Espero el sistema de módulos que monte para visualizar lo que escribo funcione, siento que puede ayudarme a alimentar esto mucho mas y ver en que se convierte si un baúl de recuerdos polvoriento, o si sirve de cofre lleno de arena con 1 tesoro dentro.
2 No espero algo cronológico, ni tampoco constante pero quiero que este en un lugar, que se pueda acceder, no aseguro que sea legible, pero estará allí</description></item><item><title>Conspiracy Runes</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/conspiracy-runes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/conspiracy-runes/</guid><description>Foto de un Tepuy (Idk cual es): Señal Wow! En una llamada de discord con amigos surgio lo siguiente en los Tepuyes hay luces y gigantes? &amp;hellip; Arboles petrificados?
🔍 Conexión con algo: Analysis de lo que dijo Daniel Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas, Paredes escritas,</description></item><item><title>Hongos titulo</title><link>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/hongos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dunkloestus.github.io/Wired-Blog/posts/hongos/</guid><description>Ejemplo 1 Ejemplo 2 Connection established. Transmission complete.
Present day, present time. Another entry logged into the wired&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>